Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series IV: Governor
  - Sub-series C: Early Swearing In (ESI) Materials
    - ESI-I through ESI-V
      - ESI-V –Indictment –U.S. v. T. Edward Sisk et al. (Box 134, Folder 58)
      - ESI-V –Letter about Leon B. Mosely (Box 134, Folder 59)
      - ESI-V –Capitol Commentary, December 6, 1978 (Box 134, Folder 60)
      - ESI-V –The Tennessean Coverage of Humphreys Clemency, September –December 1978 (Box 134, Folder 61)
    - ESI-VI –ESI-VII
      - ESI-VI –Pardons and Paroles, December 1978 Audit Report (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - ESI-VI –Pardons and Paroles Media Advisory, February 20, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - ESI-VI –Pardons and Paroles Prisoner Review Commission Enabling Act (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - ESI-VI –Pardons and Paroles News Release, March 18, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - ESI-VI –Pardons and Paroles Revisions to Statutes, April 18, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - ESI-VI –Parole Board Legislation Fiscal Note, May 2, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - ESI-VI –News Release, May 25, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 7)
      - ESI-VI –News Release, June 20, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 8)
      - ESI-VI –Miscellaneous Materials, May-June 1979 –Possible Appointments (Box 135, Folder 9)
      - ESI-VI –Miscellaneous Materials, May-June 1979 –Appointments (Box 135, Folder 10)
      - ESI-VI –Miscellaneous Drafts and Notes, undated (Box 135, Folder 11)
      - ESI-VI –Statement of Governor about Charles Traughber, April 5, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 12)
      - ESI-VI –Statement of Governor about Charles Traughber, April 18, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 13)
      - ESI-VI –Statement of Governor about Charles Traughber, June 14, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 14)
      - ESI-VI –Newspaper Clippings, February-May 1979 (1 of 2) (Box 135, Folder 15)
      - ESI-VI –Newspaper Clippings, February-May 1979 (2 of 2) (Box 135, Folder 16)
      - ESI-VII –Stipulations –Tate v. Alexander and Alexander v. Alexander, undated (Box 135, Folder 17)
      - ESI-VII –Index –Herbert Tate Newspaper File, undated (Box 135, Folder 18)
      - ESI-VII –Attorney General Opinion #104 by Tripp Hunt, January 8, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 19)
      - ESI-VII –Attorney General Opinion #105 by Richard Maxwell, January 8, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 20)
      - ESI-VII –Attorney General Opinion #109 by Robert Grunow, January 10, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 21)
      - ESI-VII –Tate v. Alexander Amended Complaint, January 22, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 22)
      - ESI-VII –Letter from Larry Woods to Lamar Alexander, January 31, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 23)
      - ESI-VII –Herbert Tate v. James Dickman Petition for Writ of Habeas Corpus, February 1, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 24)
      - ESI-VII –Transcript –Informal Review of Tennessee Board of Pardons, February 6, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 25)
      - ESI-VII –Letter from Hayes Cooney to Lamar Alexander, February 6, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 26)
      - ESI-VII –Notes Dictated to Sharon by John Jay Hooker, March 23, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 27)
      - ESI-VII –Stipulations –Herbert Tate v. James Dickman, April 18, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 28)
      - ESI-VII –Order –Herbert Tate v. James Dickman (Box 135, Folder 29)
      - ESI-VII –Herbert Tate v. Lamar Alexander –Answers to Interrogators, May 31, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 30)
      - ESI-VII –Order –Herbert Tate v. James Dickman, June 1, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 31)
      - ESI-VII –Memorandum Herbert Tate v. Lamar Alexander, June 26, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 32)
      - ESI-VII –Letter from Hayes Cooney to Lamar Alexander, July 6, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 33)
      - ESI-VII –Amended Motion and Other Documents –Melvin Alexander v. Lamar Alexander, July 26, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 34)
      - ESI-VII –Affidavit and Other Documents –Herbert Tate v. Lamar Alexander, July 26, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 35)
      - ESI-VII –Amended Motion –Herbert Tate v. Lamar Alexander, July 27, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 36)
      - ESI-VII –Answer of Defendant, Lamar Alexander, August 1, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 37)
      - ESI-VII –Plaintiff’s First Request for Admissions –Herbert Tate v. Lamar Alexander, August 15, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 38)
      - ESI-VII –Plaintiff’s First Request for Admissions –Melvin Alexander v. Lamar Alexander, August 15, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 39)
      - ESI-VII –Deposition of James Dickman –Herbert Tate v. Lamar Alexander and Melvin Alexander v. Lamar Alexander, August 30, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 40)
      - ESI-VII –Deposition of Harold Bradley –Herbert Tate v. Lamar Alexander and Melvin Alexander v. Lamar Alexander, August 30, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 41)
      - ESI-VII –Deposition of Thomas Hull –Herbert Tate v. Lamar Alexander and Melvin Alexander v. Lamar Alexander, September 5, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 42)
    - ESI-VII
      - ESI-VII –Deposition of William Koch –Herbert Tate v. Harold Bradley and Melvin Alexander v. Lamar Alexander, September 5, 1979 (Box 136, Folder 1)
      - ESI-VII –Deposition of Fred Thompson -Herbert Tate v. Harold Bradley and Melvin Alexander v. Lamar Alexander, September 5, 1979 (Box 136, Folder 2)
      - ESI-VII –Deposition of Herbert Tate –Herbert Tate v. Lamar Alexander and Melvin Alexander v. Lamar Alexander, September 6, 1979 (Box 136, Folder 3)
      - ESI-VII –Deposition of William Leech –Herbert Tate v. Harold Bradley and Melvin Alexander v. Lamar Alexander, September 11, 1979 (Box 136, Folder 4)
      - ESI-VII –Responses of Defendant Lamar Alexander –Herbert Tate v. Lamar Alexander, September 27, 1979 (Box 136, Folder 5)
      - ESI-VII –Amended Responses of Defendant Lamar Alexander –Herbert Tate v. Lamar Alexander, September 27, 1979 (Box 136, Folder 6)
      - ESI-VII –Responses of Defendant Lamar Alexander – Melvin Alexander v. Lamar Alexander, undated (1 of 2) (Box 136, Folder 7)
      - ESI-VII –Responses of Defendant Lamar Alexander –Melvin Alexander v. Lamar Alexander, undated (2 of 2) (Box 136, Folder 8)
      - ESI-VII –News Releases, January-September 1979 (Box 136, Folder 9)
      - ESI-VII –Deposition of Lamar Alexander -Herbert Tate v. Lamar Alexander and Melvin Alexander v. Lamar Alexander, October 23, 1979 (Box 136, Folder 10)
      - ESI-VII –Amended Motion for Summary Judgment of Dismissal, January 15, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 11)
      - ESI-VII –Response of Plaintiff’s to Defendant’s Original and Amended Motion for Summary Judgment, February 18, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 12)
      - ESI-VII –Order and Memorandum of Denial of Summary Judgment, May 19, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 13)
      - ESI-VII –Memorandum in Support of Motion for Summary Judgment on Behalf of Defendants Bradley and Dickman, June 1980 (Box 136, Folder 14)
      - ESI-VII –Plaintiff’s Second Request for Admissions, July 10, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 15)
      - ESI-VII –Responses of Defendant Lamar Alexander to Plaintiff’s Second Request for Admissions, July 1980 (Box 136, Folder 16)
      - ESI-VII –Brief in Opposition to Plaintiff’s Motion for Summary Judgment, October 10, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 17)
      - ESI-VII –Motion for Leave to Amend Complaint, October 10, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 18)
      - ESI-VII –Amendment to Complaint, October 10, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 19)
      - ESI-VII –Brief in Support of Motion to Amend, October 10, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 20)
      - ESI-VII –Pre-Trial Order, October 24, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 21)
      - ESI-VII –Order –Clure Morton, October 30, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 22)
      - ESI-VII –Order –Clure Morton, November 17, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 23)
      - ESI-VII –Motion for Summary Judgment on Behalf of Defendants Bradley and Dickman, July 9, 1981 (Box 136, Folder 24)
      - ESI-VII –Cross Motion for Summary Judgment, July 28, 1981 (Box 136, Folder 25)
      - ESI-VII –Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff’s Cross Motion for Summary Judgment Against Defendants Bradley and Dickman, July 28, 1981 (Box 136, Folder 26)
      - ESI-VII –Plaintiff’s Second Set of Interrogatories to Defendant Lamar Alexander, July 29, 1981 (Box 136, Folder 27)
      - ESI-VII –Motion for Summary Judgment on Behalf of Defendant Lamar Alexander, July 30, 1981 (Box 136, Folder 28)
      - ESI-VII –Brief in Support of Motion for Summary Judgment Filed on Behalf of Defendant Lamar Alexander, July 30, 1981 (Box 136, Folder 29)
    - ESI-VIII
      - ESI-VIII –Cross Motion for Summary Judgment, August 10, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 1)
      - ESI-VIII –Memorandum in Support of Plaintiff’s Cross Motion for Summary Judgment Against Defendant Lamar Alexander, August 10, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 2)
      - ESI-VIII –Pre-trial Brief on Behalf of Plaintiffs, August 31, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 3)
      - ESI-VIII –Proposed Findings of Fact Filed on Behalf of Defendant Lamar Alexander, September 1981 (Box 137, Folder 4)
      - ESI-VIII –Trial Brief on Behalf of Defendant Lamar Alexander, September 1981 (Box 137, Folder 5)
      - ESI-VIII –Pre-Trial Brief on Behalf of Defendants Bradley and Dickman, September 4, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 6)
      - ESI-VIII –Stipulations, September 9, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 7)
      - ESI-VIII –Additional Stipulations, September 14, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 8)
      - ESI-VIII –Plaintiffs’ Proposed Findings of Fact, September 14, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 9)
      - ESI-VIII –Answers to Plaintiffs’ Second Set of Interrogatories, September 15, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 10)
      - ESI-VIII –Order and Memorandum –Thomas Wiseman, November 30, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 11)
      - ESI-VIII –Notice of Appeal, December 18, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 12)
      - ESI-VIII –Order –Thomas Wiseman, December 23, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 13)
      - ESI-VIII –Notice of Composition of Record and Issues on Appeal, December 28, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 14)
      - ESI-VIII –Brief of Plaintiff Appellant Melvin Alexander, April 8, 1982 (Box 137, Folder 15)
      - ESI-VIII –Joint Appendix on Appeal, April 8, 1982 (Box 137, Folder 16)
      - ESI-VIII –Brief on Appellees Bradley and Dickman, May 11, 1982 (Box 137, Folder 17)
      - ESI-VIII –Brief for Defendant Lamar Alexander, June 9, 1982 (Box 137, Folder 18)
      - ESI-VIII –Judgment and Decision of U. S. Court of Appeals, May 3, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 19)
      - ESI-VIII –Order of the Court –Thomas Wiseman, July 15, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 20)
      - ESI-VIII –Motion for Summary Judgment Filed on Behalf of Defendant Lamar Alexander, August 1983 (Box 137, Folder 21)
      - ESI-VIII –Brief in Support of Motion for Award of Attorney’s Fees, August 29, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 22)
      - ESI-VIII –Brief in Opposition to Motion for Award of Attorney’s Fees, September 1983 (Box 137, Folder 23)
      - ESI-VIII –Motion for Extension of Time, September 1, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 24)
      - ESI-VIII –Plaintiff Melvin Alexander’s Motion for Summary Judgment, September 23, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 25)
      - ESI-VIII –Plaintiff’s Brief in Support of Motion for Summary Judgment, September 23, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 26)
    - ESI-VIII
      - ESI-VIII –Brief of Defendant Lamar Alexander in Opposition to Plaintiff’s Motion to Alter and Amend, October 1983 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - ESI-VIII –Order and Memorandum Opinion of Judge Thomas Wiseman, October 13-14, 1983 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - ESI-VIII –Plaintiff’s Motion to Alter or Amend, October 21, 1983 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - ESI-VIII –Plaintiff’s Motion to Alter or Amend, November 2, 1983 (Box 138, Folder 4)
      - ESI-VIII –Chronology of Events –Key to ESI-I (N) (Box 138, Folder 5)
      - ESI-VIII –Chronology of Events –ESI-II to ESI-IV (A) (N) (Box 138, Folder 6)
      - ESI-VIII –Chronology of Events –ESI-IV (B) to ESI-V (A) (N) (Box 138, Folder 7)
      - ESI-VIII –Chronology of Events –ESI-V (B) to ESI-VI (B) (Box 138, Folder 8)
      - ESI-VIII –Chronology of Events –ESI-VI (B) (N) to ESI-VI (C) (N) (Box 138, Folder 9)
      - ESI-VIII –Chronology of Events –ESI-VII to ESI-VII (N) (Box 138, Folder 10)
      - ESI-VIII –Chronology of Events –ESI-VIII to Tape Index (Box 138, Folder 11)
      - ESI-VIII –U.S. News and World Report, January 29, 1978 (Box 138, Folder 12)
      - ESI-VIII –Index of Newspaper Articles (Box 138, Folder 13)
      - ESI-VIII –Newspaper Clippings –Alcoholic Beverage Commission (Box 138, Folder 14)
      - ESI-VIII –Newspaper Clippings –Attorney General (Box 138, Folder 15)
      - ESI-VIII –Newspaper Clippings –Audits (Box 138, Folder 16)
      - ESI-VIII –Newspaper Clippings –Arthur Brandon (Box 138, Folder 17)
      - ESI-VIII –Newspaper Clippings –Lear Jet (Box 138, Folder 18)
      - ESI-VIII –Newspaper Clippings –Safety/ Tennessee Bureau of Investigation (Box 138, Folder 19)
      - ESI-VIII –Correspondence (Box 138, Folder 20)
    - Early Swearing In –Writings
      - Book Proposal –Draft First Chapter (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - Book Proposal –Newspaper Clippings (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - Book Proposal –Movie Marie Newspaper Clippings (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - Book Proposal –Writing Sample (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - Book Proposal –Draft Chapters, December 11, 1984 (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Book Outline, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - Book Proposal –Goal for Book, January 7, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 7)
      - Book Proposal –Goal for Book, January 8, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Book Index, January 9, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 9)
      - Book Proposal –Excerpts, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 10)
      - Book Proposal –Chapter Briefs (Box 139, Folder 11)
      - Book Proposal –Notes and Outlines, February 1985 (Box 139, Folder 12)
      - Book Draft, February 5, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Early Swearing In –Writings
      - Book Draft, January 21, 1985 (1 of 2) (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Book Draft, January 21, 1985 (2 of 2) (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - Book Draft –To Editor/Publisher, February 20, 1985 (1 of 2) (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - Book Draft –To Editor/Publisher, February 20, 1985 (2 of 2) (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Early Swearing In –Writings
      - Book Draft (1 of 2) (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Book Draft (2 of 2) (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - Book Draft –Chapters 1 and 2 (Box 141, Folder 3)
      - Book Draft –Chapters 3 and 4 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - Book Draft –Chapters 5 and 6 (Box 141, Folder 5)
      - Book Draft –Chapters 7 and 8 (Box 141, Folder 6)
      - Book Draft –Chapters 9 and 10 (Box 141, Folder 7)
      - Book Draft –Chapters 11 through 15 (Box 141, Folder 8)
      - Book Draft –Chapters 16 through 26 (Box 141, Folder 9)
      - Book Draft –“Inauguration” (Box 141, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - Sub-series D: 1982 Campaign
    - Campaign Records
      - Alexander Area Coordinators (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - Alexander Committee Schedules, July - December 1981 - Jim Haslam (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - Alexander Committee Office Staff (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - Alexander Committee Secretarial Personnel (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - Alexander Committee Staff information, July 7, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 5)
      - Alexander Committee Staff Papers (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - “Alexander Band” information (Box 142, Folder 7)
      - Alexander State Chairman Coordinator list (Box 142, Folder 8)
      - Announcement Text - Draft, February 28, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 9)
      - “Band” Correspondence (Box 142, Folder 10)
      - “Band” organization memo (Box 142, Folder 11)
      - “Band” speech (Box 142, Folder 12)
      - Biographical information - Lamar Alexander (Box 142, Folder 13)
      - Biographical information - Honey Alexander (Box 142, Folder 14)
      - Blue Book Sheets (Box 142, Folder 15)
      - Board and Commission Appointments by County - Anderson - Cumberland (Box 142, Folder 16)
      - Board and Commission Appointments by County - Davidson (Box 142, Folder 17)
      - Board and Commission Appointments by County - Decatur - Humphreys (Box 142, Folder 18)
      - Board and Commission Appointments by County - Jackson - Morgan (Box 142, Folder 19)
      - Board and Commission Appointments by County - Obion - Sevier (Box 142, Folder 20)
      - Board and Commission Appointments by County - Shelby - Wilson; out of state (Box 142, Folder 21)
      - Bulk mailings information (Box 142, Folder 22)
      - Business reply mail (Box 142, Folder 23)
      - Call log, July 15, 1981 - August 31, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 24)
      - Call log, September 1, 1981 - October 15, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 25)
      - Call log, October 16, 1981 - November 13, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 26)
      - Call log, November 16, 1981 - January 7, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 27)
      - Campaign Law (Box 142, Folder 28)
      - Campaign Study, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 29)
      - Company representatives list (Box 142, Folder 30)
      - Consultants - Doug Bailey (1 of 2) (Box 142, Folder 31)
      - Consultants - Doug Bailey (2 of 2) (Box 142, Folder 32)
    - Campaign Records
      - Contracts - Bailey/Deardourff; Wiland and Associates (Box 143, Folder 1)
      - Contracts and agreements (Box 143, Folder 2)
      - Area Coordinators and County Chairmen (Box 143, Folder 3)
      - Coordinators information files (Box 143, Folder 4)
      - Coordinators meeting, August 29, 1981 (Box 143, Folder 5)
      - County codes (Box 143, Folder 6)
      - County contacts (Box 143, Folder 7)
      - County political files (Box 143, Folder 8)
      - Direct mailing #1 - responses - no check (1 of 2) (Box 143, Folder 9)
      - Direct mailing #1 - responses - no check (2 of 2) (Box 143, Folder 10)
      - Direct mailing #2 - responses - no check (Box 143, Folder 11)
      - Direct mail, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 12)
      - Election - candidates for the House of Representatives (Box 143, Folder 13)
      - Election returns - Democrat primary, August 5, 1982; Republican Primary – August 5, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 14)
      - Election returns - Counties, 1978, 1982 Republican primary (Box 143, Folder 15)
      - Election returns - General election, November 2, 1982 - Blount County (Box 143, Folder 16)
      - Forms - Batch headers; contributor source document (Box 143, Folder 17)
      - Forms -Batch transmittal sheets (Box 143, Folder 18)
      - Forms - change of name/ address (Box 143, Folder 19)
      - Forms - consolidations (Box 143, Folder 20)
      - Forms - delete incorrect information (Box 143, Folder 21)
      - Forms - record delete (Box 143, Folder 22)
      - Form letters (Box 143, Folder 23)
      - Forms - miscellaneous changes (Box 143, Folder 24)
      - Government appointments (Box 143, Folder 25)
      - Governor’s staff (Box 143, Folder 26)
      - Issues - Coal - Claiborne County (Box 143, Folder 27)
      - Issues - Education - Teachers - Speeches, plans, letters (Box 143, Folder 28)
      - Issues - Education - Teachers - Speeches, plans, letters, newspaper clippings (Box 143, Folder 29)
      - Jaycees - contacts (Box 143, Folder 30)
      - Lease agreement - CRC Equities, Inc. (Box 143, Folder 31)
      - Legal matters - Brad Reed (Box 143, Folder 32)
    - Campaign Records
      - Lions of Tennessee - Official Directory, 1980-81 (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - Lobbyists lists, January - February 1982 (1 of 2) (Box 144, Folder 2)
      - Lobbyists lists, January - February 1982 (2 of 2) (Box 144, Folder 3)
      - Mailings - Atlantic List Company - confirmations (Box 144, Folder 4)
      - Mailings - Christmas card lists (Box 144, Folder 5)
      - Mailing lists - County chairmen (Box 144, Folder 6)
      - Mailing list - Jim Fuller (Box 144, Folder 7)
      - Mailing lists - Governor’s staff (Box 144, Folder 8)
      - Mailings - Pre-announcement (Box 144, Folder 9)
      - Mailing list - State of Tennessee (Box 144, Folder 10)
      - Mailing lists (Box 144, Folder 11)
      - Maps of Tennessee (Box 144, Folder 12)
      - Market Opinion Research Questionnaire (Box 144, Folder 13)
      - Memphis Political Structure (Box 144, Folder 14)
      - Minorities - contacts (Box 144, Folder 15)
      - Minorities - receptions for the black community (Box 144, Folder 16)
      - Minorities - black ministers - contact lists (Box 144, Folder 17)
      - Move to 121 21st. Avenue North, Suite 204 (Box 144, Folder 18)
      - Nashville to Memphis flights (Box 144, Folder 19)
      - “Nissan Project” - vocational training (Box 144, Folder 20)
      - Nominating petition (Box 144, Folder 21)
      - Occupation codes (Box 144, Folder 22)
      - Office Administration Majors (Box 144, Folder 23)
      - Organizational meetings (Box 144, Folder 24)
    - Campaign Records
      - “Project” notes - Virginia Parker (Box 145, Folder 1)
      - Plan for Re-election, pp. 1 - 29 (Box 145, Folder 2)
      - Plan for Re-election, pp. 30 - 47 (2 copies) (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - Plan for Re-election, pp. 48 - 80 (Box 145, Folder 4)
      - Plan for Re-election, pp. 81 - 113 (Box 145, Folder 5)
      - Plan for Re-election, pp. 114 - 135 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - Plan for Re-election, pp. 136 - 157 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - Policy - political planning from 1st. Administration (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - Political phone calls (Box 145, Folder 9)
      - Political phone calls, July 20 - 24, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - Political organization - county evaluation forms (1 of 2) (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - Political organization - county evaluation forms (2 of 2) (Box 145, Folder 12)
      - Political organization - county chairmen – process sheet (Box 145, Folder 13)
      - Political organization - county chairmen (Box 145, Folder 14)
      - Political organization plan (Box 145, Folder 15)
      - “Point to Point with Carol Lawrence”, February 6, 1982 - transcript (Box 145, Folder 16)
      - Postal service information (Box 145, Folder 17)
      - Primary Night Speech, August 5, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 18)
      - Project 1996: A Bi-Centennial Countdown for Restoring Community Living (Box 145, Folder 19)
      - QWIP Systems information (Box 145, Folder 20)
      - Red Tape Cutters List (Box 145, Folder 21)
      - Regional meetings, September 1982 (Box 145, Folder 22)
      - College Republicans Club Chairmen List (Box 145, Folder 23)
      - Republican County Chairmen (Box 145, Folder 24)
      - Republican County Chairmen List (Box 145, Folder 25)
    - Campaign Records
      - Republican Executive Committee - Roster Knox County, 1980 - 81 (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - Republican Governor’s List (Box 146, Folder 2)
      - Republican Leadership list (Box 146, Folder 3)
      - Republican Party - request for campaign directed list (Box 146, Folder 4)
      - Republican Party roster (Box 146, Folder 5)
      - Republican Party schedule (Box 146, Folder 6)
      - 1981 Republican Women’s Chairmen by county (Box 146, Folder 7)
      - Research - Market Opinion Polls (Box 146, Folder 8)
      - Research - “A Survey of Voter Attitudes in the State of Tennessee” – Peter D. Hart Research Associates, April 1983 (Box 146, Folder 9)
      - Residence furniture (Box 146, Folder 10)
      - Sample letters (Box 146, Folder 11)
      - Schedule forms (Box 146, Folder 12)
      - Signatures (Box 146, Folder 13)
      - Southern Bankers Directory, Spring 1981 (Box 146, Folder 14)
      - Staff Memos (Box 146, Folder 15)
      - Staff memos/information (1 of 4) (Box 146, Folder 16)
      - Staff memos/information (2 of 4) (Box 146, Folder 17)
      - Staff memos/information (3 of 4) (Box 146, Folder 18)
      - Staff memos/information (4 of 4) (Box 146, Folder 19)
      - Staff - resumes of applicants (Box 146, Folder 20)
      - Staff positions - resumes (Box 146, Folder 21)
      - State Executive Committee - list (Box 146, Folder 22)
      - State Finance Organization for, 1978 (Box 146, Folder 23)
      - State of the State Address, February 16, 1982 - Bailey draft with changes (Box 146, Folder 24)
      - State of the State Address to the Ninety-Second General Assembly of the State of Tennessee (Second Session) by Lamar Alexander, Governor, March 8, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 25)
      - State of Tennessee - employment application (Box 146, Folder 26)